You know about the Black Panther Party, but what about the White Panther Party?
Founded in 1968 by poet and rock band manager John Sinclair,
the White Panther Party was created to support the Black Panther Party
and fight white supremacy, capitalism, and state violence.
And yes, they were white.
But they weren't trying to lead, though.
They followed the leadership of black revolutionaries.
The White Panther Party is now the Panther Party, and I am a member of that party.
You can go join them, too, at thepantherparty.com.
And no, it's not just for white people.
We got rid of the white part and just named it the Panther Party.
We work in tandem with the Black Panther Party.
We do not separate from each other.
We support each other, and we see each other as comrades, not allies.
Go check out the bpp.us.
That is the new Black Panther website.
We are about to roll out some very aggressive, revolutionary organizing
for communities and community survivals.
Some plans to organize communities across the nation
and form solidarity with all kinds of movements.
The Brown Berets, the Palestine movement, the American Indian movement,
the Rednecks, the veterans, the patriots, all that good stuff.
We're coming back.
All of us are coming back.
It's like the 1960s all over again.
As always, love you, fam.
Thank you so much.